Badminton, is a game played as singles (where one person plays against one person) or doubles (where two people play against two people).
羽毛球是一项可以进行单打（一人对一人）或双打（两人对两人）的运动。
The object of the game is for you or your team to win 2 sets faster than your opponent.
比赛的目标是你或你的队伍比对手更快赢下两局。
To win a set, you must score 21 points and be at least two points ahead.
要赢下一局，你必须先得到21分，并且至少领先对手2分。
If the scores are 20-20 for example, the game carries on until one player or pair has a two point lead.
例如，如果比分是20比20，比赛将继续进行，直到某位选手或某组搭档领先2分。
Okay then, so how do you score these points?
那么，该如何获得这些分数呢？
To score a point, you must aim to hit the shuttlecock, which is usually cork with feathers with your racket over the net and onto your opponent's floor without the opponent returning the favour.
要得分，你必须用球拍把羽毛球（通常由软木和羽毛制成）击过球网，落到对方场地上，并且让对手无法把球回击过来。
The court is 13.4m long and 6.1m wide, and the net is 1.55 m above the ground.
球场长13.4米，宽6.1米，球网距离地面1.55米。
Pay attention to these lines, as the boundaries are different for singles and doubles.
请注意这些边线，因为单打和双打的界线不同。
To start the game, a player must serve the shuttlecock below the waist.
比赛开始时，发球必须在腰部以下完成。
The shuttlecock must travel over the net and land in the areas defined for a serve to be legal.
羽毛球必须越过球网，并落在规定的发球区域内，发球才算合法。
If the shuttlecock is hit onto the lines - this also counts as a point.
如果羽毛球落在线上，也算得分。
The opponent will then try and return the shuttlecock and make you miss returning it back.
接着，对手会尝试把球回击，并让你无法成功回球。
This can go back and forth and is known as a 'rally'.
这样双方会不断来回击球，这被称为一个回合（rally）。
Remember, the aim of the game is to hit the shuttlecock onto your opponents floor, and these are the area's you're aiming for.
记住，比赛的目标是把羽毛球打到对方场地，而这些就是你需要瞄准的区域。
There are several shots you can utilise to try and win points.
你可以运用多种击球方式来争取得分。
These include: Forehand ,backhand, slice, touch and smash.
这些击球方式包括：正手、反手、切球、轻吊球和扣杀。
Hitting the shuttlecock over a net onto the floor so that your opponent can't return it sounds simple enough, but in badminton - it's very easy to lose points.
把羽毛球击过球网并落到地面，让对手无法回球，听起来很简单，但在羽毛球比赛中，失分其实非常容易。
There's a lot of things you can't do in badminton.
在羽毛球比赛中，有很多事情是不能做的。
You cannot hit the shuttlecock outside the area of play.
你不能把羽毛球打出比赛场地。
You cannot hit the shuttlecock twice in succession.
你不能连续击球两次。
You cannot touch the net.
你不能触碰球网。
You cannot hit the shuttlecock into the net and it land on your side of the court.
你不能把球打到网上，并让它落回自己这一侧的场地。
You cannot touch the shuttlecock with any part of your body except with the racket and as earlier mentioned; you must serve the shuttlecock legally.
除了球拍外，你不能用身体任何部位触碰羽毛球；另外，正如前面提到的，发球必须符合规则。
If you commit any of these errors, this results in your opponents being awarded a point.
如果你犯了以上任何一种错误，对手将被判得一分。
Once a player or pair has won a point, they are also awarded the next serve.
一名选手或一组选手赢得一分后，也将获得下一次发球权。
Once a player or a pair has won 21 points and is at least 2 points ahead, they win a set.
当一名选手或一组选手获得21分，并至少领先2分时，他们便赢下一局。
First pair to win 3 sets faster than their opponent … wins.
率先赢得3局的一方获胜。
Now that's basically badminton in a nutshell, but there's a few things you'll need to understand before playing or going to a game.
以上就是羽毛球规则的基本概述，不过在真正打球或观看比赛之前，还有几点需要了解。
For example … Fault.
例如：犯规（Fault）。
At any point, if the referee notices any of these infractions: Let.
在比赛过程中，如果裁判发现以下任何违规情况，就会判 Let（重发球/重赛）。
Unlike Tennis, if the shuttlecock hits the net, it counts!
与网球不同，羽毛球碰到球网后仍然算有效！
Lets are generally called when something unexpected has interrupted.
通常，当比赛受到意外情况干扰时，会判 Let（重赛）。
Here's a list of common lets.
下面是一些常见的需要判 Let 的情况。
In this case, the point must be replayed.
在这种情况下，这一分需要重新进行。
30th Point If in the rare instance that a score reaches 29-29, the person who scores the 30th point wins the set without having to gain a two point lead.
第30分规则：在极少数情况下，如果比分来到29比29，先获得第30分的一方直接赢下该局，无需再领先2分。
As you can tell, Badminton is an extremely fast sport and it looks difficult, but as you watch or play Badminton, the rules will become clear.
正如你所看到的，羽毛球是一项节奏极快的运动，看起来可能很难，但随着你观看或亲自参与比赛，规则自然会变得清晰。